the show with our movers and shakers
segment where we're going to track a
whole host of stocks which are buzzing
in trade. Uh we do have Yash joining in
on ICIC Lombard. That stock is under
pressure. Yash, go ahead.
>> Well, as far as the numbers for the
third quarter on IC Lombard are
concerned on the top line, decent
performance. The net earn premium grew
at about 13% but operationally the
numbers seemed very weak. The net
commission grew about 15 1.5% total
expenses grew about 16%. But
operationally as I said the numbers look
very weak. Underwriting loss that
increased uh by about 132%. Uh operating
profit fell by about 17% as a result of
these two. The PAT also saw a decline of
about 9% this despite the investment
income uh that being higher by about
42%.
uh combined ratio because of the weak
underwriting performance shot up to
104.5 as compared to 102.7
which was again a negative and two
biggest segments for ICICI Lombard motor
and health though saw significant growth
in topline in their respective top line
that is the premium growth but
underwriting loss remained a worry in
both these two segments the motor
underwriting loss shot up by about 137%
or 13 or 1.37 times and the underring
getting loss on the health retail size
that also shot up by about 134%. So of
course top line 13% growth which was
decent for ICIC Lombard but
operationally the number tends to get a
lot weaker and that's reflecting on the
stock today.
>> Okay. All right. Uh thanks very much for
that Yash. So that's on ICIL Lombard. We
do have the WPI in back to the equity
market. We have Purvanka which is flying
away in today's trading session. Soonal
tell us why. Uh you know we've been
talking about how realy stocks have been
under pressure. The nifty realy index is
down 20% uh from 52- week high. So
there's been some fear around demand
concerns. Uh Purvankara reported its
quarter 3 update and it has been strong.
There are no two ways about it.
Pre-sales up 17% on a Y basis up 7% on a
sequential basis to come in at 1414 K
rupees. Uh yes the growth has slowed
down but it still remains. Uh volumes
are up 4% on a Y basis. You do have
collections which is very important for
any royalty company to be able to
collect the money for the bookings that
they have made. So that is up 22% on a Y
basis. The company also says they handed
over 1.23 million square ft delivering
1,116 homes which is another important
metric to track and during 9 months they
had a total salable area launched which
was at 2.83 million square ft and
including that there were some new phase
launches as well. So good commentary
coming in but of course we need to
understand whether these demand concerns
stay whether they are going to see it
going forward all of this is something
that we'll be tracking closely but for
today the stock is higher by 11 12% this
is on our radar but we now go across to
will